- Okay, see you later.
- Good news.
(Sheldon:)I finally have a handle on my
idea for three-person chess.
(Leonard:)That is good news. Bye.
(Sheldon:)Uh, do you know
how I solved
the balanced center
combat-area problem?
Five words:
(Sheldon:)transitional quadrilateral
to triangular tessellation.
(Leonard:)That... that's brilliant.
(Sheldon:)It's what I do.
(Sheldon:)But wait, there's more.
(Sheldon:)I also invented
two new chess pieces.
(Sheldon:)The serpent...
and the old woman.
(Leonard:)Okay, now I have to ask.
What do they do?
(Sheldon:)When the serpent slithers
to an opposing player's piece,
(Sheldon:)that piece
is considered poisoned
(Sheldon:)and will die
after two more moves.
(Leonard:)All right.
(Sheldon:)Unless... it gets to
the old woman in time,
(Sheldon:)in which case
she sucks out the poison,